<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Dale Bartolome &#8211; Reminiscent</title>
	<atom:link href="http://reminiscent.ml/author/dale/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://reminiscent.ml</link>
	<description>Your quick source of designer fragrance decants</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 13:22:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.4.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://reminiscent.ml/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/cropped-icon-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Dale Bartolome &#8211; Reminiscent</title>
	<link>http://reminiscent.ml</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Fake Perfumes Are Everywhere! Here&#8217;s How You Can Avoid Them</title>
		<link>http://reminiscent.ml/fake-perfumes-are-everywhere-heres-how-you-can-avoid-them/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dale Bartolome]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 20:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://reminiscent.ml/?p=615</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The audacity of these sellers to even call fake perfumes as &#8220;Authentic US Tester Perfume&#8221; is so infuriating. These rogues may have already sold us</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://reminiscent.ml/fake-perfumes-are-everywhere-heres-how-you-can-avoid-them/">Fake Perfumes Are Everywhere! Here&#8217;s How You Can Avoid Them</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://reminiscent.ml">Reminiscent</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The audacity of these sellers to even call fake perfumes as &#8220;Authentic US Tester Perfume&#8221; is so infuriating. These rogues may have already sold us some, only for us to find out we&#8217;ve been sold a fugazi; or worse, not even knowing they were fake and were priced on par with the real ones you can buy on outlet stores and malls. No matter what we&#8217;ve been through, we can all agree to a single common goal: <strong>THIS MUST BE STOPPED!</strong></p>



<p>These types of markets exist due to demand. If we put an end to the driving force of their business, they will all be gone&#8211;sooner or later. The first step towards this is to prevent people from buying from them. To do this, we must let people know about the dangers of buying fake perfumes and the things to look for to identify if a certain fragrance is real or fake.</p>



<p>These will be discussed in this blog. Be sure to <a href="#share">share</a> this around once you&#8217;ve finished reading.</p>



<h4 class="has-text-align-center">Here are the things you should look for to distinguish real and fake perfumes:</h4>



<h2>Declaration</h2>



<p>This is the first thing you&#8217;re supposed to see in a product posting/ad. Based on observations, sellers of fake perfumes often use these words. So if you spot these, you know it&#8217;s fake:</p>



<ul><li>Authentic US/Dubai/Singapore Tester</li><li>Class A/OEM</li><li>Original Tester</li><li>Overruns</li></ul>



<p>There are lots more to list but at least you get the point.</p>



<p>The easiest way to know, however, is to ask the seller. If you ask &#8220;is this original/authentic?&#8221; and their response is anything else other than a simple yes, then it&#8217;s fake.</p>



<p>Although, testers do exist. These are original perfumes supposedly not for retail sales as these were packaged specifically for testing purposes. Agents use these to let customers know how the fragrance smells. Testers will never have the same packaging as the retail versions.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-text-align-center"><p>If you&#8217;re hesitant to buy testers but badly wanted to test a fragrance without having to go out of the comforts of your home, buy decants online instead. <strong>Reminiscent offers <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="http://reminiscent.ml/#about" target="_blank">Decants</a> of different scents you might be interested in. Be sure to check out our <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="http://reminiscent.ml/#shop" target="_blank">Shop</a>.</strong></p></blockquote>



<h2>Physical Appearance and Packaging</h2>



<p>This part is quite tricky as some fake perfumes are terribly incredible in copying the qualities of the real perfume&#8217;s bottle and packaging. Still, you can spot a fake perfume even just by the aesthetics. Here are the things you should check:</p>



<ul><li><strong>Printed Text</strong> &#8211; Watch out for typographical errors. World-renown brands have the highest standards when it comes to quality control. There is no way they would get away with errors and wrong spellings in their packaging. If these mistakes are present, then the item is fake.</li><li><strong>Batch Code</strong> &#8211; The codes on the bottom/back of the perfume bottle must match those on the box. You can request a picture of multiple boxes of their stocks. They&#8217;re not supposed to have the same batch codes. If they do, it&#8217;s a red flag. You can also search the batch code on Google + the keyword &#8216;fake?&#8217; to know if this batch code is common among fake perfumes.</li><li><strong>Close Up Pictures</strong> &#8211; Most fakes can&#8217;t copy the sprayer of the real ones. Fakes also seem to use either darker or lighter colors of ink in their packaging. Always search for pictures of real perfumes and compare it with what the seller posts or shows you. If you&#8217;re used to the upscale taste, it&#8217;s easy to know if it&#8217;s real or fake.</li></ul>



<h4>If something doesn&#8217;t feel right, trust your doubtful intuition.</h4>



<ul><li><strong>Price Tag</strong> &#8211; Once this is present, it&#8217;s almost always legit. Look for the price tags of the top retail and department stores, both local <em>(Rustan&#8217;s, Watsons, SM Dept. Store, etc.)</em> and international <em>(Sephora, Macy&#8217;s, Marshall&#8217;s, etc.)</em> Some online sellers are selling mall pull-outs and I can confirm they&#8217;re authentic. Just be sure to look out for fraudsters who might have stolen photos from other sellers.</li><li><strong>Paper Bags and Freebies</strong> &#8211; Fraudsters love keeping their items for sale as fancy and attractive as possible. Most of them even go to the extent of producing lame paper bags carrying the brand of the fake perfumes they sell. Real perfumes are usually packaged with the retailer&#8217;s paper bags. Most brands don&#8217;t have their paper bags. Official sample vials and cards are the most common freebies that come with authentic fragrances. If someone is offering you another big bottle as a freebie, be doubtful.</li></ul>



<h2>Pricing</h2>



<p>This is the easiest way to spot fake perfumes. If they&#8217;re too good to be true, then they definitely aren&#8217;t true. Here are the pricing patters I have observed from sellers of fake perfumes:</p>



<ul><li><strong>Same Prices</strong> &#8211;  From Niche fragrances to designers, from higher-tier designers to mid-range, from Chanel and Dior to Bvlgari and Versace. They&#8217;re all priced the same simply because they&#8217;re fake.</li><li><strong>Bundle Price</strong> &#8211; Sellers of fake perfumes often use offers such as &#8216;buy one, take one&#8217; and &#8216;buy one, take 50% off on your next bottle&#8217; to attract customers. If they&#8217;re willing to give these offers, they were sourced cheaply.</li><li><strong>Reseller Price</strong> &#8211; Some of these &#8216;business-minded&#8217; sellers even offer special pricing for wholesalers, which is highly doubtful. We know that outlet and retail stores must meet certain standards in order to apply as resellers or consign products from a perfume brand&#8217;s distributor. If a seller has this kind of offer, it&#8217;s because the fragrances are fake.</li></ul>



<h2>Actual Smell</h2>



<p>Nothing beats the reliability of actual testing in identifying real and fake perfumes. This is where testers come in handy. Ask an in-store sales agent to have you test the fragrance or ask for a sample. If you can&#8217;t go out, you can order samples and <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="http://reminiscent.ml/#about" target="_blank"><strong>decants</strong></a> online. Reminiscent offers a variety of decants for you to try, cash on delivery and you can even use free shipping and discount vouchers. Just head over to our <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="http://reminiscent.ml/#shop" target="_blank"><strong>shop</strong></a> to see our decants.</p>



<h2>What&#8217;s Wrong With Buying Fake Perfumes, Anyway?</h2>



<p>Most of us wouldn&#8217;t ever know how fake fragrances are made and where they even come from. We don&#8217;t know what they consist of and we can&#8217;t hold any company liable if these products bring hazards to our health.</p>



<p>Moreover, fake perfume sales and distribution are considered underground. They pay little to no taxes and they don&#8217;t provide legitimate jobs. They destroy the perfume market as they drive away and steal potential customers of official sellers.</p>



<p><a name="share"></a></p>



<h4 class="has-text-align-center"><a name="share"></a>It&#8217;s only right for us to do our part in keeping the perfume market healthy. Make everyone aware of this by sharing this blog around.</h4>



<p></p>



<p>Thank you for your time and I hope you enjoy reading. Feel free to explore our website for more useful content worthy of your time. You are also welcome to join our discussions in our Facebook Page. <strong><a href="https://www.facebook.com/reminiscent.ml/posts/131214518545723" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Click Here</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://reminiscent.ml/fake-perfumes-are-everywhere-heres-how-you-can-avoid-them/">Fake Perfumes Are Everywhere! Here&#8217;s How You Can Avoid Them</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://reminiscent.ml">Reminiscent</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>5 Common Fragrance Mistakes by Filipinos</title>
		<link>http://reminiscent.ml/common-fragrance-mistakes-made-by-filipinos/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dale Bartolome]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 20:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://reminiscent.ml/?p=534</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We can&#8217;t expect people to be good instantly at something they&#8217;re not used to doing. This concisely applies to Filipinos and their fragrance habits. There&#8217;s</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://reminiscent.ml/common-fragrance-mistakes-made-by-filipinos/">5 Common Fragrance Mistakes by Filipinos</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://reminiscent.ml">Reminiscent</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>We can&#8217;t expect people to be good instantly at something they&#8217;re not used to doing. This concisely applies to Filipinos and their fragrance habits. There&#8217;s actually a lot of bad practices going on with regards to applying fragrances, and this even goes throughout the globe. We just can&#8217;t seem to notice much of it as it&#8217;s what most people got used to already. <strong>But let&#8217;s take this opportunity to be constructive, efficient, and improve more than ever.</strong></p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-text-align-center"><p><strong><em>I listed below the five (5) common fragrance mistakes by Filipinos, including some helpful recommendations.</em></strong></p><cite> </cite></blockquote>



<h2>Rubbing the Skin</h2>



<p>This is the most common mistake ever. It&#8217;s possible that this was heavily influenced by local mainstream entertainment, particularly <em>Teleseryes</em>. Actors tend to portray roles of either the elite preparing to go on a daily office duty or an economically-challenged individual tidying up before a job interview. We see them spraying on their wrists and immediately rub it onto their neck or behind the ear. I must admit, even I used to do this back in my early days in high school and college.</p>



<p>Sorry to say this, but what we see in <em>T.V.</em> is wrong.</p>



<p>Rubbing your skin right after spraying a fragrance almost always tend to make the top notes fade away. Aside from damaging the essence, the heat produced in rubbing your skin together. Sometimes, this might even cause skin irritation depending on your skin type or the fragrance&#8217;s composition. Since you&#8217;ve read this, take this cautionary advice: <strong>never ever do this again.</strong></p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-text-align-center"><p><em><strong>Just spray it on. That&#8217;s it.</strong><br><strong>Where to spray? Read on.</strong></em></p><cite> </cite></blockquote>



<h2>Spraying on the Wrong Spots</h2>



<p>Some people spray fragrances all over their body. This is actually a case-to-case basis. If you&#8217;re spraying a body mist or a body spray, it&#8217;s acceptable. But the common fragrances in Eau de Cologne (EDC), Eau de Toilette (EDT), and Eau de Parfum (EDP) concentrations aren&#8217;t supposed to be applied like that. Aside from wasting precious juice from spraying too much <em>(you&#8217;ll read more about this forward)</em>, a fragrance&#8217;s projection won&#8217;t work as it&#8217;s supposed to be.</p>



<p>Some spots of the body doesn&#8217;t have the optimal temperature and activity <em>(pulse point)</em> for a fragrance to perform and project properly. Moreover, wearing layers of clothes can hinder a fragrance from ever evaporating out, leaving no opportunity for it to be smelled by others <em>(and even you)</em>.</p>



<p><strong>Areas I don&#8217;t recommend:</strong></p>



<ul><li>Chest: When the fragrance evaporates from your chest, it goes directly to your nose. You&#8217;ll inevitable smell it all the time up to the point of disgust and deciding to rub it off.</li></ul>



<ul><li>Abdomen: This area lacks enough temperature and pulse, leaving no opportunity for your fragrance to stand out. Also, this isn&#8217;t really an area somebody intends to sniff when trying to smell you.</li></ul>



<ul><li>Neck: The alcohol content of your fragrance can irritate your neck, especially when you&#8217;ve just shaved.</li></ul>



<ul><li>Wrists: Even though this spot has the optimal temperature and pulse points, this spot can easily be rubbed off when you&#8217;re sitting in the office.</li></ul>



<ul><li>Hair: Your hair is vulnerable. Some fragrances react too violently when sprayed on hair. Also, there&#8217;s no point in spraying in this area. Even the cheapest common shampoos around give off pleasant smell on our hair anyway.</li></ul>



<ul><li>Back: Nobody ever raises your shirt just to smell your back, even when you&#8217;re an <em>Angkas</em> Rider.</li></ul>



<p><strong>Here are the spots where I recommend you to spray:</strong></p>



<ul><li>Behind your ears</li></ul>



<ul><li>Nape</li></ul>



<ul><li>Both sides of your collarbone or collar of your shirt</li></ul>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-text-align-center"><p><em><strong><em>Efficiency</em> is doing things right;</strong></em><br><em><strong><em>effectiveness</em> is doing the right things.</strong></em></p><cite> </cite></blockquote>



<h2>Overspraying</h2>



<p>Emptying half of your fragrance bottle for a special occasion will never be necessary. You don&#8217;t want to waste much of an expensive fragrance, or even be the center of attention quietly yelling &#8220;I smell good!&#8221;</p>



<p>In addition, too much alcohol and fragrance oil drying up can be irritable to the skin, if not dangerous.</p>



<p>My recommendation?</p>



<ul><li>Three (3) sprays for potent fragrances: one (1) behind each ear and one (1) on the nape.</li></ul>



<ul><li>Five (5) sprays for fresher fragrances that need to perform better: same as above, but adding one (1) on each side of the collar, which makes it five (5).</li></ul>



<ul><li>Two (2) sprays for evening, indoor, or intimate setting: just one (1) behind each ear.</li></ul>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-text-align-center"><p><em>Remember:<br><strong>LESS IS MORE</strong></em></p><cite>  </cite></blockquote>



<h2>Wearing The Wrong Fragrance For An Occasion or Season</h2>



<p>There are hundreds of scents and it&#8217;s confusing to find out which fragrance to wear during this and that. <strong>Bad news:</strong> Most Filipinos are not familiar with the different notes. The process of finding out what scents they like and need to wear on a certain occasion or season can feel daunting.; <strong>Good news:</strong> This article can be helpful in knowing about the fragrance wheel and scent families before you decide on what to wear during the day, during the night, on a special occasion, an outdoor activity, or indoor office setting.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img src="http://reminiscent.ml/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/1-fragrance-wheel.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-537" srcset="http://reminiscent.ml/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/1-fragrance-wheel.jpg 800w, http://reminiscent.ml/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/1-fragrance-wheel-300x300.jpg 300w, http://reminiscent.ml/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/1-fragrance-wheel-150x150.jpg 150w, http://reminiscent.ml/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/1-fragrance-wheel-768x767.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" /></figure>



<p>To give you better understanding, let me mention examples using the most popular fragrances in the market:</p>



<ul><li><strong>Giorgio Armani Acqua di Gio:</strong> Citrus, Aromatic, Aquatic. Mainly composed of fresh notes. Perfect for daytime during the summer. Safe to wear in office setting.</li><li><strong>Dolce &amp; Gabbana Light Blue:</strong> Fruity, Floral, Woody. A fresh fragrance with a hint of sexy vibe. Great for daytime during the summer. Attractive compliment-netter in office setting.</li><li><strong>Yves Saint Laurent La Nuit de L&#8217;homme:</strong> Aromatic, Spicy, Woody. A masculine fragrance with explosive spicy accord. Perfect for cold intimate nights.</li><li><a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="http://reminiscent.ml/issey-miyake-leau-dissey-pour-homme/" target="_blank"><strong>Issey Miyake L&#8217;eau d&#8217;Issey Pour Homme:</strong></a> Citrus. Aquatic. Spicy. A classic masculine fragrance that is both fresh and attractive. One of the most versatile fragrances in the market. Safe to wear anytime at any occasion or setting.</li></ul>



<p>Reading articles and reviews is a good practice that can be helpful in deciding what fragrance to wear. However, buying <a href="http://reminiscent.ml/#decants" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">decants</a> and actually testing them on yourself is still the best thing to do. <a href="http://reminiscent.ml/#decants" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Decants</a> don&#8217;t cost that much anyway.</p>



<p>Reminiscent is selling fragrance decants for as low as Php 200 each.<br><a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="http://reminiscent.ml/#shop" target="_blank">Click here</a> to know more.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-text-align-center"><p><em><strong>&#8220;There&#8217;s a right time and place for everything&#8230;&#8221;</strong></em><br>&#8211;<em>Professor Oak (Pokemon)</em></p><cite><em> </em><br></cite></blockquote>



<h2>Terrible Purchase Decisions</h2>



<p>Let&#8217;s keep this simple and straightforward. Here are the keypoints:</p>



<ul><li><strong>Don&#8217;t buy fakes.</strong> Even those who claim to sell <em>&#8216;authentic US tester&#8217;</em>, <em>&#8216;authentic Dubai tester&#8217;</em>, <em>&#8216;authentic Singapore tester&#8217;</em>, <em>&#8216;overruns&#8217;</em>, <em>&#8216;OEM&#8217;</em>, <em>&#8216;class A&#8217;</em>, and any other term**&#8230; They&#8217;re all fake. These fakes, given we have from zero to few knowledge about their source and material composition, can be hazardous to human skin. Aside from that, they don&#8217;t really smell good unlike the real ones from authorized and trusted sellers. Performance and longevity is even worse.<br><em>(**Original testers do exist though. Only packaging differs from those being sold at retails stores.)</em></li></ul>



<ul><li><strong>Choose your <em>cheapies</em> carefully.</strong> This includes all those &#8216;inspired&#8217; fragrances you see from micro to small enterprises and popular fast-fashion brands. You get what you pay for. There are only a few gems around those cheap marbles. Since they&#8217;re keeping the production costs as low as possible, don&#8217;t expect the same pleasant scent and performance that is present in more expensive designer and niche fragrances. Most cheap fragrances are linear: what you smell at first is what you smell until it fades away.</li></ul>



<ul><li><strong>Avoid blind buys.</strong> Never buy a fragrance you don&#8217;t like and would probably almost never wear. You&#8217;ll just end up either not using it or disposing it without getting back the actual amount you spent on it. It can leave you fund-less and can hinder your purchase of the real deal.</li></ul>



<p>Reminiscent is here to help you on this matter. We offer decants of original designer fragrances, cheaper than retail price most of the time. Be sure to check out our <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="http://reminiscent.ml/#shop" target="_blank">shop</a> to see what fragrances you&#8217;re interested on, and don&#8217;t be shy to ask around. Hit us up on <a href="http://m.me/reminiscent.ml" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Messenger</a> or join our discussions on <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="http://facebook.com/reminiscent.ml" target="_blank">Facebook</a>.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-text-align-center"><p><strong><em>We hope you enjoyed reading this article. Feel free to share this around and let everyone know about the best practices when it comes to fragrances.</em></strong></p></blockquote>



<p></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://reminiscent.ml/common-fragrance-mistakes-made-by-filipinos/">5 Common Fragrance Mistakes by Filipinos</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://reminiscent.ml">Reminiscent</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rem, our Chatbot, is Now Online!</title>
		<link>http://reminiscent.ml/rem-our-chatbot-is-now-online/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dale Bartolome]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 17:09:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News and Updates]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://reminiscent.ml/?p=524</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We are glad to announce that Reminiscent&#8217;s Facebook Page and Messenger is now 24/7 online. Through hard work and dedication, we were able to create</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://reminiscent.ml/rem-our-chatbot-is-now-online/">Rem, our Chatbot, is Now Online!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://reminiscent.ml">Reminiscent</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>We are glad to announce that <strong>Reminiscent&#8217;s <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="http://facebook.com/reminiscent.ml" target="_blank">Facebook Page</a></strong> and <strong><a href="http://m.me/reminiscent.ml" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Messenger</a></strong> is now 24/7 online. Through hard work and dedication, we were able to create Rem. She will stand as Reminiscent&#8217;s Chatbot who will be in our frontlines to help you, our customers, with regards to your inquiries and concerns involving <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="http://reminiscent.ml/#decants" target="_blank">our products</a> and other services we could possibly provide.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-text-align-center"><p><strong><em>To experience Rem&#8217;s service, <a href="#experience">click here</a>.</em></strong></p><p><em><strong>If you&#8217;re interested in Rem&#8217;s story, feel free to browse below.</strong></em></p></blockquote>



<p></p>



<h2>Who is Rem? Why her?</h2>



<p><strong>Rem</strong> is a character from the anime &#8220;Re:Zero.&#8221; She is a <strong>young, hardworking maid </strong>who<strong> upholds respect </strong>and<strong> high standards for quality of work and service.</strong> We chose her to represent and take care of Reminiscent while we are away since we deeply trust her capabilities and personality.</p>



<h2>How is Rem connected to Reminiscent?</h2>



<p>Rem has a <strong>strong sense of smell.</strong> In the anime, Rem was able to smell the witch&#8217;s scent on Subaru even from a distance. I <em>(Dale, founder of Reminiscent)</em> believe that <strong>I relate to Rem on that aspect.</strong></p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-text-align-center"><p><em><strong>Reminiscent&#8217;s brand name origin composes of three important words. (and even Rem&#8217;s name)</strong></em></p></blockquote>



<ul><li><strong>Reminiscent</strong>, which means tending to remind one of something. A fascination of the past caused by real-time experiences.</li><li><strong>Mini</strong>, which is a synonym for small. This describes the decant bottles that we use.</li><li><strong>Scent</strong>, which pertains to the fragrances we decant.</li></ul>



<a id="experience"><h2>How can I experience Rem&#8217;s service?</h2></a>



<p>Just check us out on <strong><a href="http://m.me/reminiscent.ml" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Facebook Messenger</a></strong> and click on &#8216;Get Started&#8217; or &#8216;Chat with Rem&#8217;. Rem would be glad to serve you your needs with regards to <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="http://reminiscent.ml/#shop" target="_blank">Reminiscent&#8217;s mini scents</a>. If you ever encounter technical issues with Rem, or even suggestions and feedback, feel free to type a free-form message. We highly appreciate these and immediately address these types of concerns.</p>



<p></p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-text-align-center"><p><strong><em>Thank you very much for your support! We wish you to stay confident at all times and smell great.</em></strong></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://reminiscent.ml/rem-our-chatbot-is-now-online/">Rem, our Chatbot, is Now Online!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://reminiscent.ml">Reminiscent</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Our New Website is Now Live!</title>
		<link>http://reminiscent.ml/our-new-website-is-now-live/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dale Bartolome]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 09:48:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News and Updates]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://reminiscent.ml/?p=507</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After months of hard work and dedication, we are excited to officially announce the launch of our website! Come check us out at reminiscent.ml Our</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://reminiscent.ml/our-new-website-is-now-live/">Our New Website is Now Live!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://reminiscent.ml">Reminiscent</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>After months of hard work and dedication, we are excited to officially announce the launch of our website! Come check us out at <a href="http://reminiscent.ml/">reminiscent.ml</a></p>



<p>Our website offers our viewers a user-friendly, easy to navigate fresh new website, allowing our viewers to easily browse for our available fragrance decants and information about fragrances in general. </p>



<p>We are constantly updating our content with new offerings, products, special announcements, news and events, useful articles, and discounts or promo vouchers you can use in shopping through <strong><a href="http://shopee.ph/reminiscent.ml" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Reminiscent&#8217;s Shopee Page.</a></strong></p>



<p>We hope you enjoy our website! For any questions, suggestions, feedback or comments, please leave us a message through Messenger. <a href="http://m.me/reminiscent.ml" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">m.me/reminiscent.ml</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://reminiscent.ml/our-new-website-is-now-live/">Our New Website is Now Live!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://reminiscent.ml">Reminiscent</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Page Caching using disk: enhanced (Page is feed) 
Lazy Loading (feed)
Minified using disk

Served from: localhost @ 2020-05-27 01:48:52 by W3 Total Cache
-->