<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Blog &#8211; Reminiscent</title>
	<atom:link href="http://reminiscent.ml/category/blog/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://reminiscent.ml</link>
	<description>Your quick source of designer fragrance decants</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 21:20:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.4.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://reminiscent.ml/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/cropped-icon-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Blog &#8211; Reminiscent</title>
	<link>http://reminiscent.ml</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>5 Common Fragrance Mistakes by Filipinos</title>
		<link>http://reminiscent.ml/common-fragrance-mistakes-made-by-filipinos/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dale Bartolome]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 20:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://reminiscent.ml/?p=534</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There&#8217;s actually a lot of bad practices going on with regards to applying fragrances. We just can&#8217;t seem to notice much of it as it&#8217;s</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://reminiscent.ml/common-fragrance-mistakes-made-by-filipinos/">5 Common Fragrance Mistakes by Filipinos</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://reminiscent.ml">Reminiscent</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>There&#8217;s actually a lot of bad practices going on with regards to applying fragrances. We just can&#8217;t seem to notice much of it as it&#8217;s what most people got used to already. <strong>But let&#8217;s take this opportunity to be constructive and efficient more than ever.</strong></p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-text-align-center"><p><strong><em>I listed below the five (5) common fragrance mistakes by Filipinos, including some helpful recommendations.</em></strong></p><cite> </cite></blockquote>



<h2>Rubbing the Skin</h2>



<p>This is the most common mistake being committed even throughout the world. It&#8217;s possible that this was heavily influenced by local mainstream entertainment, particularly <em>Teleseryes</em>. Actors tend to portray roles of either the elite preparing to go on a daily office duty or an economically-challenged individual tidying up before a job interview. We see them spraying on their wrists and immediately rub it onto their neck or behind the ear. Sorry to say, what you see in <em>T.V.</em> is wrong.</p>



<p>Rubbing your skin right after spraying a fragrance almost always tend to make the top notes fade away. Aside from damaging the essence, the heat produced in rubbing your skin together. Sometimes, this might even cause skin irritation depending on your skin type or the fragrance&#8217;s composition. Since you&#8217;ve read this, take this cautionary advice: <strong>never ever do this again.</strong></p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-text-align-center"><p><em><strong>Just spray it on. That&#8217;s it.</strong><br><strong>Where to spray? Read on.</strong></em></p><cite> </cite></blockquote>



<h2>Spraying on the Wrong Spots</h2>



<p>Some people spray fragrances all over their body. This is actually a case-to-case basis. If you&#8217;re spraying a body mist or a body spray, it&#8217;s acceptable. But the common fragrances in Eau de Cologne (EDC), Eau de Toilette (EDT), and Eau de Parfum (EDP) concentrations aren&#8217;t supposed to be applied like that. Aside from wasting precious juice from spraying too much <em>(you&#8217;ll read more about this forward)</em>, a fragrance&#8217;s projection won&#8217;t work as it&#8217;s supposed to be.</p>



<p>Some spots of the body doesn&#8217;t have the optimal temperature and activity <em>(pulse point)</em> for a fragrance to perform and project properly. Moreover, wearing layers of clothes can hinder a fragrance from ever evaporating out, leaving no opportunity for it to be smelled by others <em>(and even you)</em>.</p>



<p><strong>Areas I don&#8217;t recommend:</strong></p>



<ul><li>Chest: When the fragrance evaporates from your chest, it goes directly to your nose. You&#8217;ll inevitable smell it all the time up to the point of disgust and deciding to rub it off.</li><li>Abdomen: This area lacks enough temperature and pulse, leaving no opportunity for your fragrance to stand out. Also, this isn&#8217;t really an area somebody intends to sniff when trying to smell you.</li><li>Neck: The alcohol content of your fragrance can irritate your neck, especially when you&#8217;ve just shaved.</li><li>Wrists: Even though this spot has the optimal temperature and pulse points, this spot can easily be rubbed off when you&#8217;re sitting in the office.</li><li>Hair: Your hair is vulnerable. Some fragrances react too violently when sprayed on hair. Also, there&#8217;s no point in spraying in this area. Even the cheapest common shampoos around give off pleasant smell on our hair anyway.</li><li>Back: Nobody ever raises your shirt just to smell your back, even when you&#8217;re an Angkas Rider.</li></ul>



<p><strong>Here are the spots where I recommend you to spray:</strong></p>



<ul><li>Behind your ears</li><li>Nape</li><li>Both sides of your collarbone or collar of your shirt</li></ul>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-text-align-center"><p><em><strong><em>Efficiency</em> is doing things right;</strong></em><br><em><strong><em>effectiveness</em> is doing the right things.</strong></em></p><cite> </cite></blockquote>



<h2>Overspraying</h2>



<p>Emptying half of your fragrance bottle for a special occasion will never be necessary. You don&#8217;t want to waste much of an expensive fragrance, or even be the center of attention quietly yelling &#8220;I smell good!&#8221;</p>



<p>In addition, too much alcohol and fragrance oil drying up can be irritable to the skin, if not dangerous.</p>



<p>My recommendation?</p>



<ul><li>Three (3) sprays for potent fragrances: one (1) behind each ear and one (1) on the nape.</li><li>Five (5) sprays for fresher fragrances that need to perform better: same as above, but adding one (1) on each side of the collar, which makes it five (5).</li><li>Two (2) sprays for evening, indoor, or intimate setting: just one (1) behind each ear.</li></ul>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-text-align-center"><p><em>Remember:<br><strong>LESS IS MORE</strong></em></p><cite>  </cite></blockquote>



<h2>Wearing The Wrong Fragrance For An Occasion or Season</h2>



<p>There are hundreds of scents and it&#8217;s confusing to find out which fragrance to wear during this and that. Bad news: Most Filipinos are not familiar with the different notes. The process of finding out what scents they like and need to wear on a certain occasion or season can feel daunting.; Good news: This article can be helpful in knowing about the fragrance wheel and scent families before you decide on what to wear during the day, during the night, on a special occasion, an outdoor activity, or indoor office setting.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img src="http://reminiscent.ml/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/1-fragrance-wheel.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-537" srcset="http://reminiscent.ml/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/1-fragrance-wheel.jpg 800w, http://reminiscent.ml/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/1-fragrance-wheel-300x300.jpg 300w, http://reminiscent.ml/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/1-fragrance-wheel-150x150.jpg 150w, http://reminiscent.ml/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/1-fragrance-wheel-768x767.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" /></figure>



<p>To give you better understanding, let me mention examples using the most popular fragrances in the market:</p>



<ul><li><strong>Giorgio Armani Acqua di Gio:</strong> Citrus, Aromatic, Aquatic. Mainly composed of fresh notes. Perfect for daytime during the summer. Safe to wear in office setting.</li><li><strong>Dolce &amp; Gabbana Light Blue:</strong> Fruity, Floral, Woody. A fresh fragrance with a hint of sexy vibe. Great for daytime during the summer. Attractive compliment-netter in office setting.</li><li><strong>Yves Saint Laurent La Nuit de L&#8217;homme:</strong> Aromatic, Spicy, Woody. A masculine fragrance with explosive spicy accord. Perfect for cold intimate nights.</li><li><a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="http://reminiscent.ml/issey-miyake-leau-dissey-pour-homme/" target="_blank"><strong>Issey Miyake L&#8217;eau d&#8217;Issey Pour Homme:</strong></a> Citrus. Aquatic. Spicy. A classic masculine fragrance that is both fresh and attractive. One of the most versatile fragrances in the market. Safe to wear anytime at any occasion or setting.</li></ul>



<p>Reading articles and reviews is a good practice that can be helpful in deciding what fragrance to wear. However, buying <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="http://reminiscent.ml/#decant" target="_blank">decants</a> and actually testing them on yourself is still the best thing to do. <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="http://reminiscent.ml/#decant" target="_blank">Decants</a> don&#8217;t cost that much anyway.</p>



<p>Reminiscent is selling fragrance decants for as low as Php 200 each.<br><a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="http://reminiscent.ml/#shop" target="_blank">Click here</a> to know more.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-text-align-center"><p><em><strong>&#8220;There&#8217;s a right time and place for everything&#8230;&#8221;</strong></em><br>&#8211;<em>Professor Oak (Pokemon)</em></p><cite><em> </em><br></cite></blockquote>



<h2>Terrible Purchase Decisions</h2>



<p>Let&#8217;s keep this simple and straightforward. Here are the keypoints:</p>



<ul><li><strong>Don&#8217;t buy fakes.</strong> Even those who claim to sell <em>&#8216;authentic US tester&#8217;</em>, <em>&#8216;authentic Dubai tester&#8217;</em>, <em>&#8216;authentic Singapore tester&#8217;</em>, <em>&#8216;overruns&#8217;</em>, <em>&#8216;OEM&#8217;</em>, <em>&#8216;class A&#8217;</em>, and any other term**&#8230; They&#8217;re all fake. These fakes, given we have from zero to few knowledge about their source and material composition, can be hazardous to human skin. Aside from that, they don&#8217;t really smell good unlike the real ones from authorized and trusted sellers. Performance and longevity is even worse.<br><em>(**Original testers do exist though. Only packaging differs from those being sold at retails stores.)</em></li><li><strong>Choose your <em>cheapies</em> carefully.</strong> This includes all those &#8216;inspired&#8217; fragrances you see from micro to small enterprises and popular fast-fashion brands. You get what you pay for. There are only a few gems around those cheap marbles. Since they&#8217;re keeping the production costs as low as possible, don&#8217;t expect the same pleasant scent and performance that is present in more expensive designer and niche fragrances. Most cheap fragrances are linear: what you smell at first is what you smell until it fades away.</li><li><strong>Avoid blind buys.</strong> Never buy a fragrance you don&#8217;t like and would probably almost never wear. You&#8217;ll just end up either not using it or disposing it without getting back the actual amount you spent on it. It can leave you fund-less and can hinder your purchase of the real deal.</li></ul>



<p>Reminiscent is here to help you on this matter. We offer decants of original designer fragrances, cheaper than retail price most of the time. Be sure to check out our <a href="http://reminiscent.ml/#shop" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">shop</a> to see what fragrances you&#8217;re interested on, and don&#8217;t be shy to ask around. Hit us up on <a href="http://re.mnis.cf/msgr" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Messenger</a> or join our discussions on <a href="http://facebook.com/reminiscent.ml" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Facebook</a>.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-text-align-center"><p><strong><em>We hope you enjoyed reading this article. Feel free to share this around and let everyone know about the best practices when it comes to fragrances.</em></strong></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://reminiscent.ml/common-fragrance-mistakes-made-by-filipinos/">5 Common Fragrance Mistakes by Filipinos</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://reminiscent.ml">Reminiscent</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Page Caching using disk: enhanced (Page is feed) 
Lazy Loading (feed)
Minified using disk

Served from: localhost @ 2020-05-10 05:21:20 by W3 Total Cache
-->